Guide to the Yale College Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Georges May as dean, circa 1936-1971; Accession 1980-A-017
  - Health, Education and Welfare, U.S. Department of (Box 34, Folder 457)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 34, Folder 458)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 459)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 460)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 34, Folder 461)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 34, Folder 462)
  - History, Department of
    - 1959-1962 (Box 34, Folder 463)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 34, Folder 464)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 465)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 466)
  - History of Art, Department of, 1968-1969 (Box 34, Folder 467)
  - Honor societies, 1947-1950 (Box 34, Folder 468)
  - Honor system, 1949-1950 (Box 34, Folder 469)
  - Honors, Committee on
    - 1932-1958 (Box 34, Folder 470)
    - 1959-1965 (Box 35, Folder 471)
    - 1966 (Box 35, Folder 472)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 35, Folder 473)
  - Honors and Special Projects, Committee on, 1969-1971 (Box 35, Folder 474 - 475)
  - Housing, Parking and Communications, 1970-1972 (Box 35, Folder 476)
  - Humanities, Division of, 1946-1958 (Box 35, Folder 477)
  - Human Relations, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 478)
  - I - General
    - 1959-1965 (Box 35, Folder 479)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 480)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 35, Folder 481)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 35, Folder 482)
  - Industrial Administration, 1952-1959 (Box 35, Folder 483)
  - Institute of International Education, 1964-1966 (Box 35, Folder 484)
  - Institute of Social Science, 1967-1970 (Box 35, Folder 485 - 486)
  - Interim Disciplinary Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 35, Folder 487)
  - International Office
    - 1964-1968 (Box 35, Folder 488)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 489)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 490)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 491)
  - J - General
    - 1959-1965 (Box 36, Folder 492)
    - 1965-1967 (Box 36, Folder 493)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 36, Folder 494)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 495)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 496)
  - Job availabilities, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 497)
  - Job inquiries, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 498)
  - Junior Faculty Fellowships
    - 1962-1963 Apr (Box 36, Folder 499)
    - 1963 Sep - 1964 Aug (Box 36, Folder 500)
    - 1964 Sep - Dec (Box 36, Folder 501)
    - 1965 (Box 36, Folder 502)
    - 1966 (Box 37, Folder 503)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 504)
    - Natural Sciences, 1967-1971 (Box 37, Folder 505 - 508)
    - Social Sciences, 1967-1971 (Box 37, Folder 509 - 512)
  - Junior and term appointments, 1968-1971 (Box 38, Folder 513 - 515)
  - K - General
    - 1958-1965 (Box 38, Folder 516)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 38, Folder 517)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 38, Folder 518)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 38, Folder 519)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 520)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 521)
  - Kilborne (Robert S.) Memorial Traveling Scholarship, 1964-1967 (Box 38, Folder 522)
  - L - General
    - 1960-1965 (Box 38, Folder 523)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 38, Folder 524)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 38, Folder 525)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 38, Folder 526)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 39, Folder 527)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 39, Folder 528)
  - Language Laboratory, 1964-1969 (Box 39, Folder 529)
  - Language teaching at Yale, 1967-1969 (Box 39, Folder 530 - 531)
  - Languages, Committee on, 1968-1971 (Box 39, Folder 532 - 534)
  - Latin American Affairs, 1942 (Box 39, Folder 535)
  - Leaves of absence
    - for 1965-1966 (1964-1965) (Box 39, Folder 536)
    - for 1967-1968 (1966-1967) (Box 39, Folder 537 - 538)
    - for 1968-1969 (1967-1968) (Box 39, Folder 539)
  - Library Committee
    - 1963-1965 (Box 40, Folder 540)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 541)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 40, Folder 542)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 40, Folder 543)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 544)
    - Report on the Library by Henry W. Broude, 1964 August (Box 40, Folder 545)
  - Liquor in Colleges, 1965, undated (Box 40, Folder 546)
  - M - General
    - 1955-1965 (Box 40, Folder 547)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 548)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 549)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 550)
    - 1969-1971 (Box 40, Folder 551)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 552)
  - Mc - General
    - 1967-1968 (Box 41, Folder 553)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 41, Folder 554)
    - 1970 (Box 41, Folder 555)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 41, Folder 556)
  - Majors, 1940-1963 (Box 41, Folder 557)
  - Manners and Morals Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 41, Folder 558)
  - Marsh, Ronald C. (Registrar of Yale College), 1954-1963 (Box 41, Folder 559)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1965-1967 (Box 41, Folder 560)
  - Master of Arts in Teaching Program, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 561)
  - May Day
    - 1970 (Box 41, Folder 562 - 563)
    - petitions, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 564 - 566)
    - publications, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 567)
  - May, Georges: personal, 1964-1970 (Box 41, Folder 568 - 570)
  - Medicine, School of, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 571)
  - Mellon Fund (See: Old Dominion Foundation), 1952-1958 (Box 41, Folder 572)
  - Modern Language Association
    - 1947-1958 (Box 41, Folder 573)
    - 1962-1965 (Box 42, Folder 574)
    - 1965 (Box 42, Folder 575)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 42, Folder 576)
    - 1968 (Box 42, Folder 577)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 42, Folder 578)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 42, Folder 579)
  - Morse College, 1968-1971 (Box 42, Folder 580 - 582)
  - Morse Fellowships
    Records of Morse College fellowships are restricted for 75 years from the date of their creation.
    - 1951-1952 (Box 42, Folder 583)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 42, Folder 584)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 42, Folder 585)
    - 1957 (Box 43, Folder 586)
    - 1958 (Box 43, Folder 587 - 588)
    - 1959 (Box 43, Folder 589 - 590)
    - 1960 (Box 43, Folder 591)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 43, Folder 592)
    - letters from former holders of Morse Fellowships, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 593)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 43, Folder 594)
    - 1961-1963 Jun (Box 44, Folder 595)
    - 1963 (Box 44, Folder 596)
    - 1963 Sep - 1965 (Box 44, Folder 597)
    - 1964 (Box 44, Folder 598)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 44, Folder 599 - 600)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 44, Folder 601)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 602 - 603)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 604 - 605)
    - 1968 (Box 45, Folder 606)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 45, Folder 607 - 608)
    - 1970 (Box 46, Folder 609)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 46, Folder 610)
  - Mount Holyoke College, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 611)
  - N - General
    - 1959-1965 (Box 46, Folder 612)
    - 1963-1968 (Box 46, Folder 613)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 46, Folder 614)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 46, Folder 615)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 46, Folder 616)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 46, Folder 617)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities
    - 1968-1969 (Box 46, Folder 618)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 46, Folder 619)
    - summer stipends, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 620)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 46, Folder 621)
  - National Science Foundation, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 622)
  - Navy, 1956-1959 (Box 47, Folder 624)
  - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1964-1969 (Box 47, Folder 625)
  - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools: accredidation, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 626 - 627)
  - New England Deans Association, 1961-1970 (Box 47, Folder 628)
  - News Bureau, 1970-1971 (Box 47, Folder 629 - 630)
  - News, Yale Daily, 1961-1966 (Box 47, Folder 631)
  - Novick, Alvin, "Report on the Function of the Laboratory in Teaching Biology", 1968 (Box 47, Folder 632)
  - O - General
    - 1961-1963 (Box 47, Folder 633)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 47, Folder 634)
    - 1966 (Box 47, Folder 635)
    - 1968-1970 (Box 47, Folder 636)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 47, Folder 637)
  - Oriental Languages, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 640)
  - P - General
    - 1956-1965 (Box 47, Folder 641)
    - 1965-1967 (Box 48, Folder 642)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 48, Folder 643)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 48, Folder 644)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 48, Folder 645)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 48, Folder 646)
  - Parietals, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 647)
  - Payroll slips, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 648)
  - Peace Corps, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 649)
  - Permanent Officers, Joint Board of
    - 1948-1961 (Box 48, Folder 650)
    - 1962-1965 (Box 48, Folder 651)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 48, Folder 652)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 48, Folder 653)
    - 1970 (Box 48, Folder 654)
    - Committee on procedures, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 655)
  - Phelps Association, 1964-1969 (Box 49, Folder 656)
  - Phi Beta Kappa
    - 1965-1967 (Box 49, Folder 657)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 49, Folder 658)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 49, Folder 659)
    - 1970 (Box 49, Folder 660)
  - Philosophy, Department of, 1962-1971 (Box 49, Folder 661 - 663)
  - Physical Science, 1964-1966 (Box 49, Folder 664)
  - Physics, Department of, 1968-1971 (Box 49, Folder 665 - 666)
  - Pierson College, 1967-1971 (Box 49, Folder 667 - 668)
  - Placement Officers, 1968-1969 (Box 49, Folder 669)
  - Police, Campus, 1964-1967 (Box 49, Folder 670)
  - Political Science, Department of, 1956-1965 (Box 49, Folder 671)
  - Political Science, Department of, 1966-1970 (Box 50, Folder 672 - 673)
  - Political Studies, Advanced, Office of, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 674)
  - Pre-Medical Committee
    - 1951-1954 (Box 50, Folder 675)
    - 1965-1968 (Box 50, Folder 676)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 50, Folder 677)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 50, Folder 678)
    - 1970 (Box 50, Folder 679)
  - Princeton University, 1958-1962, 1966-1967 (Box 50, Folder 680 - 681)
  - Prizes, 1956-1957, 1961-1971 (Box 50, Folder 682 - 683)
  - Projects Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 50, Folder 684)
  - Provost's Office
    - 1950-1962 (Box 50, Folder 685)
    - 1963-1965 (Box 50, Folder 686)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 50, Folder 687)
    - 1968 (Box 50, Folder 688)
    - 1969 (Box 51, Folder 689)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 51, Folder 690)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 51, Folder 691)
  - Provost, Charles H. Taylor Jr., 1966-1968 (Box 51, Folder 692 - 693)
  - Psychology, Department of, 1955-1970 (Box 51, Folder 694 - 696)
  - Publication Fund, proposal for, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 697)
  - Q - General, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 698)
  - R - General
    - 1955-1965 (Box 51, Folder 699)
    - 1965-1967 (Box 51, Folder 700)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 51, Folder 701)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 52, Folder 702)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 52, Folder 703)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 52, Folder 704)
  - Redecorating: requisitions, 1967-1968 (Box 52, Folder 705)
  - Registrar
    - 1968 (Box 52, Folder 706)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 52, Folder 707)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 52, Folder 708)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 52, Folder 709)
  - Registration and Schedules Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 52, Folder 710)
  - Religion, Department of, 1955-1963 (Box 52, Folder 711)
  - Religious Studies, Department of, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 712)
  - Reports, 1953-1961 (Box 52, Folder 713)
  - Requirements for the degree, 1946-1954 (Box 52, Folder 714)
  - Residential Colleges: potentialities and responsibilities, 1958-1968 (Box 52, Folder 715)
  - Riot folder, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 717)
  - Robley, Grant, Registrar, 1964-1968 (Box 53, Folder 718)
  - Romance Languages
    - 1959-1964 (Box 53, Folder 720)
    - 1964-1966 (Box 53, Folder 721)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 53, Folder 722)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 53, Folder 723)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 53, Folder 724)
    - 1971 (Box 53, Folder 725)
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps Program
    - 1960-1966 (Box 53, Folder 726)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 53, Folder 727)
    - 1969 (Box 53, Folder 728)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 53, Folder 729)
  - S - General
    - 1956-1965 (Box 54, Folder 730)
    - 1964-1967 (Box 54, Folder 731)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 54, Folder 732)
    - 1966-1969 (Box 54, Folder 733)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 734)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 735)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 54, Folder 736)
  - St. Elmo Study, 1964-1967 (Box 55, Folder 737)
  - Saturday classes, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 738)
  - Saybrook College, 1968-1971 (Box 55, Folder 739 - 741)
  - Schedule Committee, 1966-1968, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 742 - 743)
  - Scholars of the House
    - 1944-1959 (Box 55, Folder 744)
    - 1959-1965 (Box 55, Folder 745)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 55, Folder 746)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 55, Folder 747)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 55, Folder 748)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 749)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 55, Folder 750)
  - Science, 1945-1961 (Box 55, Folder 751)
  - Sciences, Biological, 1966-1967 (Box 55, Folder 752)
  - Secretary's Office
    - 1963-1965 (Box 55, Folder 753)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 55, Folder 754)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 55, Folder 755)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 55, Folder 756)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 757)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 55, Folder 758)
  - Selective Service, 1950-1967 (Box 55, Folder 759 - 760)
  - Selective Service, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 761)
  - Senior Advisory Board, 1950-1966 (Box 56, Folder 762 - 763)
  - Senior Appointments Committee, Biological Sciences (Box 56, Folder 764)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 56, Folder 765)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 56, Folder 766)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 767)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 56, Folder 768)
  - Senior Appointments Committee, Humanities
    - 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 769)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 56, Folder 770)
    - 1968 (Box 56, Folder 771)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 772)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 56, Folder 773)
  - Senior Appointments Committee, Physical Sciences
    - 1968 (Box 57, Folder 774 - 776)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 57, Folder 777)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 57, Folder 778)
  - Senior Appointments Committee, Social Sciences
    - 1965-1967 (Box 57, Folder 780)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 57, Folder 781)
    - 1968 (Box 57, Folder 782)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 57, Folder 783)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 57, Folder 784)
  - Senior Essays, 1941-1962 (Box 57, Folder 785)
  - Service Bureau, 1964-1966 (Box 58, Folder 786)
  - Silliman College, 1968-1971 (Box 58, Folder 787 - 788)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures, 1961-1962 (Box 58, Folder 789)
  - Small enrollments, 1967-1970 (Box 58, Folder 790 - 791)
  - Social Sciences, 1954-1956 (Box 58, Folder 792)
  - Sociology, Department of
    - 1965-1970 (Box 58, Folder 793)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 58, Folder 794)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 795)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 58, Folder 796)
  - Sophomore Discussion Groups in the Colleges, 1953-1962 (Box 58, Folder 797)
  - SophomoreDiscussion Groups: Letters from departments on, 1959 (Box 58, Folder 798)
  - Sophomore Discussion Groups, 1964-1966 (Box 58, Folder 799)
  - Southeast Asian Studies, 1951-1960 (Box 58, Folder 800)
  - State Board of Education, 1951-1953 (Box 58, Folder 801)
  - Statistics, 1939-1958 (Box 58, Folder 802)
  - Steering Committee
    - 1965-1968 (Box 58, Folder 803)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 804)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 59, Folder 805)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 59, Folder 806)
  - Ezra Stiles College, 1967, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 807 - 808)
  - Student Advisory Board, 1966-1968 (Box 59, Folder 809)
  - Student Advisory Committees, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 810)
  - Student Council, 1947 (Box 59, Folder 811)
  - Student Records Office
    - 1956-1963 (Box 59, Folder 812)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 59, Folder 813)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 59, Folder 814)
    - 1967-1970 (Box 59, Folder 815)
  - Student Record System, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 816)
  - Study Group on Yale College, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 817)
  - Study of the City, 1969-1971 (Box 59, Folder 818 - 819)
  - Study Skills Office, 1965-1966 (Box 59, Folder 820)
  - Summer Activities
    - 1965-1966 (Box 59, Folder 821)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 60, Folder 822)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 60, Folder 823)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 60, Folder 824)
  - Summer Language Institute, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 825)
  - Summer Programs
    - 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 826)
    - 1970 (Box 60, Folder 827 - 828)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 60, Folder 829)
  - Supplementary Services, Office of, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 830)
  - T - General
    - 1951-1965 (Box 60, Folder 831)
    - 1964-1969 (Box 60, Folder 832)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 61, Folder 833)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 61, Folder 834)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 835)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 61, Folder 836)
  - Teacher Preparation Program, 1969-1971 (Box 61, Folder 837)
  - Teaching and Learning, Committee on, 1967-1971 (Box 61, Folder 838 - 840)
  - Term Appointments, Joint Committee on, 1964-1965, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 843 - 844)
  - Thomas, (Dean) Elisabeth, 1969-1971 (Box 61, Folder 845 - 846)
  - Town-Gown Relations, Committee on, 1953-1954 (Box 61, Folder 847)
  - Transitional Year Program, 1966-1968 (Box 61, Folder 848 - 849)
  - Transitional Year Program, 1968-1969 (Box 62, Folder 850)
  - Travel expense reports, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 851)
  - Treasurer's Office
    - 1953-1962 (Box 62, Folder 852)
    - 1963-1965 (Box 62, Folder 853)
    - 1964-1966 (Box 62, Folder 854)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 62, Folder 855)
    - 1968 (Box 62, Folder 856)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 62, Folder 857)
    - 1970-1911 (Box 62, Folder 858)
  - Trumbull College, 1967-1971 (Box 62, Folder 859 - 861)
  - Tuition postponement option, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 862)
  - U - General
    - 1955-1964 (Box 62, Folder 863)
    - 1965 (Box 62, Folder 864)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 62, Folder 865)
    - 1969 (Box 62, Folder 866)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 62, Folder 867)
    - 1970 (Box 62, Folder 868)
  - Undergraduate Affairs, 1960-1966 (Box 62, Folder 869 - 870)
  - Undergraduate Officers Conference
    - 1968-1969 (Box 62, Folder 871)
    - 1969 (Box 62, Folder 872)
    - 1969 (Box 63, Folder 873)
    - 1969-1971 (Box 63, Folder 874)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 63, Folder 875 - 876)
  - Undergraduate Regulations, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1969-1970 (Box 63, Folder 877)
  - Universal Military Service, 1950-1951 (Box 63, Folder 878)
  - University Deans, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 879)
  - University Health, Board of, 1968-1970 (Box 63, Folder 880 - 881)
  - Urban Studies, 1967-1968 (Box 63, Folder 882)
  - Urban Studies, 1968-1970 (Box 64, Folder 883 - 884)
  - V - General
    - 1960-1965 (Box 64, Folder 885)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 64, Folder 886)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 64, Folder 887)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 64, Folder 888)
    - 1970 (Box 64, Folder 889)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 64, Folder 890)
  - Vassar-Yale Study, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 891)
  - W - General
    - 1961-1965 (Box 64, Folder 892)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 64, Folder 893)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 64, Folder 894)
    - 1967-1969 (Box 64, Folder 895)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 64, Folder 896)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 64, Folder 897)
  - Western trip, 1950 (Box 64, Folder 901)
  - Westminster School, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 902)
  - White House Fellows, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 903)
  - Wilkinson, (Dean) John A., 1968-1970 (Box 64, Folder 904 - 905)
  - Wilkinson, (Dean) John A., 1970-1971 (Box 65, Folder 906)
  - Wright Hall incident, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 908 - 909)
  - X - Y - Z - General
    - 1951-1965 (Box 65, Folder 910)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 65, Folder 911)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 65, Folder 912)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 65, Folder 913)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 65, Folder 914)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 65, Folder 915)
  - Yale Club of New York City, 1962-1965 (Box 65, Folder 916)
  - Yale College Banner bearing the Arms of Yale College, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 917)
  - Yale College: faculty meetings
    - 1967-1968 (Box 65, Folder 918)
    - 1969 (Box 65, Folder 919)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 65, Folder 920)
    - 1971 (Box 65, Folder 921)
  - Yale College Series, 1957-1971 (Box 65, Folder 922 - 923)
  - Yale Parking Authority, 1968-1969 (Box 65, Folder 924 - 925)
  - Yale Programs of Study, 1968-1969 (Box 65, Folder 926 - 927)
  - Zoology, Department of, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 928)
- Records of Horace Taft as dean, 1972-1975; Accession 1983-A-051
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2011
  - 1972-1973
    - American Association of University Professors (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Association of Colleges in New England (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - A.D.S. -- Administrative Data Systems (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Adjunct ranks (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Administrative Sciences (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Admissions (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Advisory committee: Humanities (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Afro-American Studies (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Alterations (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Alumni (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - American Studies (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Anthropology (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Applications for positions (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Appointment procedures (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Appointments committees (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Appointments, Junior, committee (Box 2, Folder 16 - 18)
    - Appointments, Senior, committee
      - Physical sciences (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Humanities (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Social Sciences (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Advisory committee: Biological Sciences (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Archeology (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Architecture, School of (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Art School and Art major (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Astronomy (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Athletics (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Audio visual (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Bachelors degrees (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Band (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Biology (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Biometeorology (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Blum committee (see: Series II) (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Board of Permanent Officers (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Bursary system (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Bus, shuttle (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Calendar reform (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Calhoun College (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Campus police (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Career Advisory Office (Box 4, Folder 40 - 41)
    - Chairmen -- Departmenta1 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Chairmanships (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Chairs, professorial (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Chaplain (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Chemistry (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Classics (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Co-education committee (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - College deanships (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - College Deans (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - College Masters (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Combined Literature major (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Combined Science (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Commencement (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Communications (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Computer Science (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Concilium (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Conferences (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Connecticut Humanities Council (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Contracts, policies on (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Coop (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - College Council, Yale (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Council of Masters (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Course enrollments (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Course of study -- Fall 1972 (Box 6, Folder 65 - 66)
    - Course of study for 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 67 - 70)
    - Course of study for 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 71 - 76)
    - Corporation minutes (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - College credits (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Credits to Departments (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Davenport (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Deans, University (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Deans: Meeting of undergraduate officers (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Deans conferences (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - Dean's office staff (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Debating (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Development office (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Directed studies (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Directors of Undergraduate Studies (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Divisional major I (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Divisional major II (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Dramat (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Drama School (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Early concentration (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - East and Southeast Asian Studies (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Economics (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - Engineering and Applied Science (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - English (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Enrollments, Fall 1972 (Box 9, Folder 99 - 100)
    - Executive committee Y.C. (Box 9, Folder 101 - 102)
    - Faculty advising (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - Faculty meeting minutes (Box 9, Folder 104 - 105)
    - Faculty problems (Box 10, Folder 106)
    - Faculty recommendations (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences (FAS) Executive committee (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - Fellow, Resident requests (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - Fellows of Colleges (Box 10, Folder 111)
    - Fellowships (Box 10, Folder 112)
    - Fellowship committees (Box 10, Folder 113)
    - Financial aid (Box 10, Folder 114)